[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "And when you went home Tony, what did you discover?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "I discovered the bodies of my mother, my little sister, and my cousin.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "What then happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "I was asked to come down to the precinct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "When you were made to do that, what were you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "I really -- at this moment, I really don't even know what I was thinking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "When you heard about that or when did you hear about that and what did you expect to then happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Well, when I heard about it, I was extremely overwhelmed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "That there was such a breakdown in the legal process that the medical examiner was not even spoken to by the attorneys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "EX", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "You know, I described this case as a perfect storm, everything that could go wrong in a criminal justice situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["State of New York", "Attica"]}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ":", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJS", ",", "RB", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Antonio, what has that been like for you, I mean, bad enough doing present time anyway but to be doing it -- to having falsely convicted of killing your own mother and sister and your little sister's friend, what did that do to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", ":", "TO", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "It was a nightmare, extremely nightmare of -- and not only was a nightmare, but they had me in the worst, worst maximum security prison in the State of New York which is Attica.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "The one thing you've missed most?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "New York air.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Which is pretty cold right now, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "But describe to me as best you can, how you dealt with it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "JJS", "PRP", "MD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "It was horrible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "And when you came out, Shariff, what was the first thing you wanted to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Have some New York pizza.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Shariff"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "How do you cope with that part of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Well, for many years, I felt horrible that I had to do that and that I actually did it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "When you discovered, Antonio, that he had made this revelation to your family, what did you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Well, like I told them about a few hours ago, that I have no animosity towards him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Antonio"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Do you have any hope of finding the real killer now and getting justice for your mother, your sister, and your cousin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Yeah, I have hope.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Shariff, what do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "I say yes, if he's willing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mau", "Robin"]}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Is that inevitable when two of your brothers are twins?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "WRB", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "I think we became disconnected about 12 years ago and then we last, Mau, Robin and I gravitated back towards each other a little bit and he's always been twins and the older brother and so there was a real difference.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Is it the precious outside forces of fame and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "I guess it's the difference between being in a group and being brothers in a group or being sisters in a group, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Why that one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Because it's really about lost love in all the young people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["BBC"], "LOCATION": ["Massachusetts"]}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "WRB", "``", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "NN", "CD", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "CC", ":", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "How did you met?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Well, we met on the set of Top of the Pops when \"Massachusetts\" was number one and then we had a cup of tea in the canteen of the BBC and then we had a couple in -- and (inaudible) and time stood still.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "And how do you manage that because show business is so, this is so listed with broken marriages, how have you managed to sustain such a lasting love do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Because I think we've just always been in love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "You've never looked to anyone else since she's always in love with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Well, I think we've both loved.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Hard to watch, why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "IBB: Because I hate looking myself at different ages.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "And how's the -- how's your voice on that, I mean, how is it compared to what it used to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "It's OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Did people expect you to talk about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "But, rather a nostalgia about that, did you and the Beatles hang out much or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Your brother Andy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Is that part of the progress?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "What would be your favorite memory or perhaps the big times with your brothers, not the early days (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Yeah, being around the microphone together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "ORGAN: What would you like the Bee Gees to stand for, to be remembered for, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "As song writer, beyond anything else and harmonies, you know, there was no great approach.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dolly", "Kenny"]}, "docId": "140207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "So you sang it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "I was the Dolly role and Kenny sang his role.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]